

Software Engineer

Skills

- Problem solving
- Knowledge of PHP.MYSQL and data structures
- I am an expert in HTML,CSS, JavaScript
- · Communication skills
- · I am a web designer
- Software programming languages

ADDRESS

Drigh road station cantt bazar new Igbal Abad house no 124

EMAIL

waqarelahim762@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://waqar-elahi.github.io/Dentist-Web/

SOCIAL MEDIA

https://www.linkedin.com/in/waq ar-elahi-4775042b4? utm_source=share&utm_campai gn=share_via&utm_content=prof ile&utm_medium=android_app

CONTACT NUMBER

+92-0336-856-4692

Profile

A qualified software engineer with 1 years experienced with an excellence skill in analyzing and modifying existing software, as well as developing, designing, and testing end-user applications that match user needs – all using software programming languages.

Education

Govt boys secondary school | 2017

Matric of Computer Science

Aptch institute of computer | 2024

Intermediate in Commerce from Karachi Board (in process)

Work Experience

Falaknaz&Group|March2021-2023

Security Supervisor.

- 1 Year as a Security Supervisor at Mega Mall
- 1 Year in Supervision and Management at Building Dynasty

Newplex .cinema | 2018-2020

Security Guard

· 2 year as a security guard at Newplex cinema

Millennium mall. | 2022-2023

Salesman

• 1 year as a Salesman at Millennium Mall